Guide to the Joan Wulff Papers 1944-2014
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
Joan Wulff Papers
1944-2014
Montana State University Library, Merrill G. Burlingame Special Collections P.O. Box 173320 Bozeman, MT 59717-3320 United States Phone (406) 994-4242 Fax (406) 994-2851 http://www.lib.montana.edu/archives/ University Archivist spcoll@www.lib.montana.edu
Collection 2591, MtBC, us
Wulff, Joan
1.7 cubic feet
The Joan Wulff Papers include correspondence, speeches, article and book manuscripts, galleys, brochures, artwork, and photographs. Topics include fly fishing, fly fishing techniques, and fly fishing equipment for women.
Biographical Note
Joan Salvato Wulff was born in 1927 in Patterson, New Jersey. She married Lee Wulff in 1966. Joan was a National Casting Champion from 1943-1960, she won the National Fisherman’s Distance Casting event against an all-male field, and was elected to the International Game Fish Association Hall of Fame in 2007. Joan is the founder of the Catskill Fly Fishing Center, Trustee of the Atlantic Salmon Federation and the International Game Fish Association, advisor to the Federation of Fly Fishers, and consultant for the R.L. Winston Rod Company.
The Wulff’s opened the Joan and Lee Wulff Fishing School in 1979. Joan has authored articles for Outdoor Life, Atlantic Salmon Journal, Fly Fisherman Magazine, and Rod and Reel later Fly Rod and Reel. Wulff also authored the books Joan’s Wulff’s Fly Casting Accuracy, Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Techniques, Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, and Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing: Expert Advice from A Woman’s Perspective.
The Joan Wulff Papers include correspondence, speeches, article and book manuscripts, galleys, brochures, artwork, and photographs. Topics include fly fishing, fly fishing techniques, and fly fishing equipment for women. Of interest are the Lee Wulff manuscripts for On a Trout Fly and For the Kids in Series two.
Series 1 Correspondence, 1964-2005
Series 2 Literary Productions, 1968-2004
Series 3 Printed Materials, 2010, 2014
Series 4 Photographs and Artwork, 1944-1999
Copyright for column artwork for articles in Rod and Reel later Fly Rod and Reel held by the magazine.
Correspondence, speeches, manuscripts, galleys, brochures, artwork, and photographs were donated by Joan Wulff on September 10, 2014. Selected VHS and monographs accompanying the donation were cataloged separately.
Fishing and Canning; Literature; Sports and Recreation; Women; Photographs
- Correspondence, 1964-2005; Series 1
  Materials in Series one contains photocopies of original correspondence collected by Ted Rogowski pertaining to the early history of the Federation of Fly Fishers. Correspondents include Ted Rogowski, Lee Wulff, Bob Wethern of the Oregon Flfishers Club, William A. Nelson of the McKenzie Flyfishers Club, Ed J. Strickland of the Federation of Flyfishers, and Gene Anderegg of the Federation of Flyfishers. The correspondence in this series are PDF scans on a CD-R disk provided by Wulff.
  - Fly Fishing History, 1964-2005 (Box-folder 1/1)
- Literary Works, 1968-2004; Series 2
  Series two consists of speeches given by Joan Wulff, article manuscripts, book manuscripts and galleys authored by Joan. Also included in Box 5 are manuscripts for Lee Wulffs books On A Trout Fly and For the Kids. Articles for Joan’s column in Rod and Reel date from November/December 1981 to May/June 1989 and Fly Rod and Reel from July/October 1989 to March 2002; illustrations for these articles include those by Gordon Allen for issues in November/December 1981-November/December 1988, Richard Harrington for issues in January/February 1989-July/October 1989, and Francis Davis for issues in November/December 1989-March 1993.
  - Speech: International Festival of Women Flyfishers, October 21-24, 1999 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Speech: Academic Awards Dinner, June 12, 2003 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Speech: International Game Fish Association Hall of Fame, 2007 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Speech: Anglers’ Club Book Night, October 23, 2008 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Speech: Atlantic Salmon Federation Dinner, November 12, 2008 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - ‘Greatest Fishing Thrill’, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - ‘Trying to Break the Women’s 80LB Test Bluefin Tuna Record’, 1968 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - ‘Garcia Girl Rods,’ Garcia Annual (Box-folder 1/9)
  - ‘Fly Fishing Schools,’ Sports Afield, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - ‘Fishing for Atlantic Salmon,’ Daiwa Annual, 1977 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - ‘Come On In, Gals, the Water’s Fine,’ Angler’s Calendar, 1978 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - ‘How Not to Be A Fly Fishing Widow’, 1979 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - ‘Tips and Techniques for the Beginning Fly Fisherman,’ Red Ball Annual, 1979 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - ‘How Much is Enough,’ Outdoor Life, 1979 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Letter to Kathleen Farmer, Need for Equipment for Women, 1980 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - ‘The Magic of Trout Fishing,’ Freshwater Fisherman, Tom Mann, 1980 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - ‘No Title Fishing School Piece,’ Atlantic Salmon Journal, Special Issue, 1980 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - ‘Drift: the Magic Movement,’ Fly Fisherman Magazine, 1981 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - ‘The Fat and Feisty Fish of Michael’s River,’ Atlantic Salmon Journal, 1982 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - ‘Trout Fishing Widows…Don’t Be One,’ Sullivan County Democrat, 1984 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - ‘The Minipi Watershed,’ Reed Books, 1998 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - ‘The Etiquette of Atlantic Salmon Fishing,’ Rod Rage, Rhea Topping, 2004 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - ‘The Evolution of A Flyfisher,’ The Gigantic Book of Fishing Stories, Nick Lyons, 2007 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - ‘Casting with A Fly Rod,’ Fly Fisherman’s Complete Guide to Fishing with A Fly Rod, Joan and Lee Wulff, 1978 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Casting Columns List, Fly Rod and Reel, 1981-2002 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - ‘Lesson in Line Twist, Outdoor Life, February 1980 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - ‘The Underhand Flip,’ Outdoor Life, April 1980 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - ‘Open Up for Distance,’ Outdoor Life, May 1980 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - ‘Easy Accuracy,’ Outdoor Life, July 1980 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - ‘Eliminate Backlash,’ Outdoor Life, August 1980 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - ‘Eliminate Backlash,’ Outdoor Life, December 1980 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - ‘Use Both Hands,’ Outdoor Life, circa 1980 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - ‘The Overhead Cast,’ Outdoor Life, circa 1980 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - ‘The Roll Cast,’ Outdoor Life, circa 1980 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - ‘Casting the Ultralights,’ Outdoor Life, circa 1980 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - ‘The Power Snap,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1981 (Box-folder 1/37)
  - ‘Saltwater Quick Cast, Rod and Reel, January/February 1982 (Box-folder 1/38)
  - ‘The First Move,’ Rod and Reel, March/April 1982 (Box-folder 1/39)
  - ‘How’s Your Grip,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1982 (Box-folder 1/40)
  - ‘Picking Leaves for Accuracy,’ Rod and Reel, July/October 1982 (Box-folder 1/41)
  - ‘Getting the Whole Picture,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1982 (Box-folder 1/42)
  - ‘Line Hand Tension,’ Rod and Reel, July/August 1983 (Box-folder 1/43)
  - ‘Coiling Line on the Retrieve,’ Rod and Reel, September/October 1983 (Box-folder 1/44)
  - ‘Marking Lines for Weight and Distance,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1983 (Box-folder 1/45)
  - ‘Gear for the Next Generation,’ Rod and Reel, January/February 1984 (Box-folder 1/46)
  - ‘The Roll Cast,’ Rod and Reel, March/April 1984 (Box-folder 1/47)
  - ‘Roll Pick-up with Single Haul,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1984 (Box-folder 1/48)
  - ‘Shooting Line on the Backcast,’ Rod and Reel, July/October 1984 (Box-folder 1/49)
  - ‘Hovering,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1984 (Box-folder 1/50)
  - ‘Indoor Fly Casting Practice,’ Rod and Reel, January/February 1985 (Box-folder 1/51)
  - ‘The Backcast Power Snap,’ Rod and Reel, March/April 1985 (Box-folder 1/52)
  - ‘Drift on the Backcast,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1985 (Box-folder 1/53)
  - ‘Loading on the Forward Cast,’ Rod and Reel, July/October 1985 (Box-folder 1/54)
  - ‘The Forward Power Snap,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1985 (Box-folder 1/55)
  - ‘Atlantic Salmon: Tackle and Wet Fly Coverage,’ Rod and Reel, January/February 1986 (Box-folder 1/56)
  - ‘The Quick Cast: 60 feet or more in 2-3 seconds,’ Rod and Reel, March/April 1986 (Box-folder 1/57)
  - ‘The Double Haul: Part 1,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1986 (Box-folder 1/58)
  - ‘The Double Haul: Part 2,’ Rod and Reel, July/August 1986 (Box-folder 1/59)
  - ‘The Double Haul: Part 3,’ Rod and Reel, September/October 1986 (Box-folder 1/60)
  - ‘The Single Haul,’ Rod and Reel, January/February 1987 (Box-folder 1/61)
  - ‘Fly Line Designs,’ Rod and Reel, March 1987 (Box-folder 1/62)
  - ‘Loop Control: Narrow or Wide,’ Rod and Reel, April 1987 (Box-folder 1/63)
  - ‘Loop Control: Tailing Loops,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1987 (Box-folder 1/64)
  - ‘Casting Backhanded,’ Rod and Reel, July/October 1987 (Box-folder 1/65)
  - ‘Changing Direction with False Casting,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1987 (Box-folder 1/66)
  - ‘Changing Direction without False Casting, Rod and Reel, January/February 1988 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - ‘Back To Basics: Common Faults,’ Rod and Reel, March 1988 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - ‘A Basic System for Trout Leaders,’ Rod and Reel, April 1988 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - ‘Curving Power Snaps for Circular Line Patterns,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1988 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - ‘Curving Casting Patterns: The Oval,’ Rod and Reel, July/October 1988 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - ‘Circular Casting Patterns: Air Rolls,’ Rod and Reel, November/December 1988 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - ‘The Pure Joy,’ Rod and Reel, January/February 1989 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - ‘Making It Happen: The Perfect Forward Cast Loop,’ Rod and Reel, March 1989 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - ‘The Reach Cast,’ Rod and Reel, April 1989 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - ‘Body Stances: Square to the Target for Vertical Plane Casting,’ Rod and Reel, May/June 1989 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - ‘Body Stances: Square to the Target for Vertical Plane Casting,’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/October 1989 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - ‘Taking A Casting Break,’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 1989 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - ‘Line Handling: Tangle-Free Loops for Long Casts,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1990 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - ‘Throw Me A Curve! Upstream,’ Fly Rod and Reel, March 1990 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - ‘Slack Leader Casts,’ Fly Rod and Reel, April 1990 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - ‘Dealing with Air-Resistant Bass Bugs,’ Fly Rod and Reel, May/June 1990 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - ‘Wind from Your Back: Reversing,’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/October 1990 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - ‘Headwind and Front Quartering,’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 1990 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - ‘Details and Disciplines: Wrist Action on Backcast,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1991 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - ‘Details and Disciplines: Backcast Pick-up,’ Fly Rod and Reel, March 1991 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - ‘Forearm Position at the End of the Backcast,’ Fly Rod and Reel, April 1991 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - ‘Upper Arm Movement,’ Fly Rod and Reel, May/June 1991 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - ‘Hand Action on the Forward Power Snap,’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/October 1991 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - ‘Lee, the Caster,’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 1991 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - ‘Drift To A Better Position,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1992 (Box-folder 2/25)
  - ‘Which Rod for You,’ Fly Rod and Reel, March 1992 (Box-folder 2/26)
  - ‘Details and Disciplines: The Double Haul,’ Fly Rod and Reel, April 1992 (Box-folder 2/27)
  - ‘Details and Disciplines: Slide Loading on Haul,’ Fly Rod and Reel, May/June 1992 (Box-folder 2/28)
  - ‘Long Cast Sequence: Four Strokes,’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/October 1992 (Box-folder 2/29)
  - ‘Loading the Rod,’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 1992 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - ‘Details and Disciplines: Line Hand Use,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1993 (Box-folder 2/31)
  - ‘The Change-Your-Fly Pickup,’ Fly Rod and Reel, March 1993 (Box-folder 2/32)
  - ‘Casting To Win,’ Fly Rod and Reel, April 1993 (Box-folder 2/33)
  - ‘Roll Cast,’ Fly Rod and Reel, May/June 1993 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - ‘Rolling Out of Trouble,’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/October 1993 (Box-folder 2/35)
  - ‘Rotation for Changing Direction,’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 1993 (Box-folder 2/36)
  - ‘Mirror Magic,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1994 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - ‘Loose the Death Grip (Sponge),’ Fly Rod and Reel, March 1994 (Box-folder 2/38)
  - ‘Two-Handed Rods,’ Fly Rod and Reel, April 1994 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - ‘Spey Casting – Part 1,’ Fly Rod and Reel, May/June 1994 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - ‘Spey Casting – Part 2 (Single-Spey),’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/October 1994 (Box-folder 2/41)
  - ‘Spey Casting – Part 3 (Double Spey),’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 1994 (Box-folder 2/42)
  - ‘Fear of Casting,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1995 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - ‘Fly Casting: (Joan Returns) Sister Anglers At Last,’ Fly Rod and Reel, May/June 1998 (Box-folder 2/44)
  - ‘Elbow Your Way To Better Casting – Part I,’ Fly Rod and Reel, September/October 1998 (Box-folder 2/45)
  - ‘The Elbow – Part II,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 1999 (Box-folder 2/46)
  - ‘Achieving Accuracy – Reprint,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 2000 (Box-folder 2/47)
  - ‘Going To the Wall,’ Fly Rod and Reel, July/August 2000 (Box-folder 2/48)
  - ‘Loop Control – Part I,’ Fly Rod and Reel, January/February 2001 (Box-folder 2/49)
  - ‘Loop Control – Part II,’ Fly Rod and Reel, June 2001 (Box-folder 2/50)
  - ‘The Drift Move,’ Fly Rod and Reel, November/December 2001 (Box-folder 2/51)
  - ‘Getting It Together or A Checklist,’ Fly Rod and Reel, March 2002 (Box-folder 2/52)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Accuracy, Manuscript (Box-folder 2/53)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Accuracy, Galleys (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Accuracy, Covers (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Accuracy, Review Copy (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Manuscript (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Manuscript (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Finished Manuscript (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Finished Manuscript (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Galleys (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Galleys (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Galleys (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Galleys (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Fishing, Galleys (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Techniques, Manuscript, 1987 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Techniques, Manuscript, 1987 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Techniques, Review Copy, 1987 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Techniques, Manuscript, 2004 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Joan Wulff’s Fly Casting Techniques, Manuscript, 2004 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Outline (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Acknowledgements (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Quotes (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Manuscript (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Manuscript (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Pull-outs/Boxes (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Photos (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Illustrations By David Shepherd (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Joan Wulff’s New Fly Casting Techniques, Suggested Covers (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Lee Wulff’s Trout on A Fly, Manuscript “Master Set” (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Lee Wulff’s Trout on A Fly, Manuscript “Master Set” (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Lee Wulff’s Let's Go Fishing, Manuscript (Box-folder 6/4)
- Printed Materials, 2010; 2014; Series 3
  Series three contains two brochures pertaining to Lee and Joan Wulff. The first provides an overview of Lee Wulff’s life; the second advertises the Wulff School of Fly Fishing founded by Lee and Joan Wulff.
  - Lee Wulff, 2010 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Wulff, School of Fly Fishing on the Beaverkill, 2014 (Box-folder 6/6)
- Photographs and Artwork, 1944-1999; Series 4
  Series four contains photos and artwork. Individuals included in the images include Lee Wulff, Joan Wulff, Jimmy Salvato, Emmett Kelly, Monte Blue, and Ed Zern. The photographs in this series are PDF scans on a CD-R disk provided by Wulff. The photograph titles were taken from the image or verso of the image, they include the number assigned to the image on the disk. The artwork in this series was created drawn by artists Dom Lupo and Gary Allen for Joan Wulff’s casting columns. This series contains photographic material that was separated from the oversize box Folder 2 and relocated to Box 5, Folder 17; the separation is denoted by an asterisk (*) next to the folder from which the images were removed. These photographs are the basis from which artist Gary Allen drew his artwork for the casting columns.
  - #1-#53 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - #1 Lee Wulff
      JW1001
    - #2 Lee Wulff
      JW2001
    - #3 Famous Clown Emmett Kelly. Joan Salvato Pert Casting Instructor. Fisherman Magazine.
      JW3002
    - #4 Lee Wulf. Lee Goes Through His Vest.
      JW4004
    - #6 Joan Salvato. Costume “Built” on Joan Salvato. Solo-Besamé Mucho. Tap Dancing. Age-18 to 20. Had Dancing School., 1944-1952
      JW6006
    - #7 Bris du Boulogne, “Little River” Event – French National Tournament, 1948
      JW7007
    - #8 Joan Salvato
      JW8008.
    - #9 Lee Wulff
      JW9009.
    - #10 Joan, circa 1950
      JW1001.
    - #11 Front Row: Billy Pate, Stu Apt, Joan, Bill Curtis. Back Row: Chico Fernandez, Mark Sosin, Curt Goridy.
      JW11011.
    - #12 Joan with Dad. Jimmy Salvato.
      JW12012.
    - #13 Celebration of Dame Juliana’s 500 Year Anniversary. Joan and Annette McLean Teaching.
      JW13013.
    - #14 William Taylor-Joan’s Casting Mentor. Ellis Newman-Sitting, 1950s
      JW14014.
    - #15 Unknown Male, Bridge Diving.
      JW15015.
    - #16 Sally Ann Brusttin, Janet, Joan and Brother Lou, Eileen Donnely, 1945
      For American Magazine. JW16016.
    - #17 Joan. At Peoria, Illinois, 1960
      National Casting Tournament or Michigan? JW17017.
    - #18 Oldham Pond. North Haledon, New Jersey. Joan-3d from Left, Peggy Buckman 4th, Far Right-Jim Tracey.
      JW18018.
    - #19 Lee Wulff. River of Ponds-Newfoundland, 1947
      Atlantic Salmon. JW19019.
    - #20 Joan Wulff
      JW20020.
    - #21 Joan Wulff. Photo Credit: Geoffey Cathers.
      JW21021.
    - #22 Oldham Pond. North Haledon, New Jersey. Patterson Casting Club Dock, Dad, Jimmy Salvato, around 1939
      Anthony Grasso, Jimmy Harris, Bob Buckman, Gary Eickman, 3 Unknown, Alice?, Joan Salvato, Peggy Buckman, Ann Bahr. JW22022.
    - #23 Joan Wulff. Salt Water Flyrodders, 1971
      Maryland. JW23023.
    - #24 Joan Wulff
      JW24024.
    - #25 American Fishing Tackle Manufacturers Association Show. Garcia Booth, circa 1971
      JW25025.
    - #26 Joan, 1960
      Warren, Michigan. American Casting Association Championships. Photo by Tom McNally. JW26026.
    - #27 Joan, circa 1956
      Louisville, Kentucky for Fisherman Magazine. JW27027.
    - #28 Joan Wulff
      JW28028.
    - #29 Joan Wulff, circa 1971 or 1972
      Allenberry, Pennsylvania. Federation of Fly Fishers. Eastern Conclave. Ray Pryzgoda (Prescott), Charles Ritz, Lee, ?. JW29029.
    - #30 Fly
      JW30030.
    - #31 Lee Wulff
      JW31031.
    - #32 Lee on the Willowemoc Stream. Catskill Mountains, New York.
      JW32032.
    - #33 Lee and Joan Wulff
      JW33033.
    - #34 Lee and Joan Wulff
      JW34034.
    - #35 Art Lee, Davit Scoll, Ray Scott
      JW35035.
    - #36 Humor Writer Ed Zern. Joan Working for Garcia and Royal Red Ball.
      JW36036.
    - #37 Lee and Joan Wulff, with Mel Krieger
      JW37037.
    - #38 Royal Red Ball Waders and Garcia Tackle, Chicago, Mid 1970s
      JW38038.
    - #39 Joan Wulff
      JW39039.
    - #40 Stu Apte, Joan, Steve Thomas at Papa Joe’s, 1999
      JW40040.
    - #41 Joan, Philadelphia Sportsman Show, 1954
      JW41041.
    - #42 Leon Martruck of 3m-Sci Anglers Mark Sosin next to Joan, circa 1971
      JW42042.
    - #43 Joan Salvato, 1966
      JW43043.
    - #44 Joan Salvato, 1954
      JW44044.
    - #45 Joan, 1960
      JW45045.
    - #46 Joan Wulff, Mrs. Ned Vespa, 1980-1982
      JW46046.
    - #47 Joan Wulff, 1988
      Steelhead-18 lbs, Skeena River, British Columbia. JW47047.
    - #48 Ben Fontainé, Leon Chandler?. American Fishing Tackle Manufacturers Association-Key Biscayne, 1966
      JW48048.
    - #49 Joan, 1960
      JW49049.
    - #50 Joan Wulff in Willowmoc-Catskill Mountains, New York State. Credit: Terry Yamagishi. Was Cover of Book Fly Casting Techniques.
      JW50050.
    - #51 Monte Blue, 1954
      JW51051.
    - #52 Joan Wulff, 1979
      In the Beaverkill. Photo by Glen Lou. JW52052.
    - #53 Joan Teaching At American Fishing Tackle Manufacturers Association Show for Garcia with Fly-O.
      JW53053.
  - #54-67 Artwork, Gary Allen, Drift, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Artwork, Dom Lupo, Outdoor Life (Box-folder Oversize/1)
  - Artwork, Gary Allen, Drift, 1979-1981* (Box-folder Oversize/2)